NYS PERB Agreements 5140
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Boards of Education: Levittown through Liberty (Box 129)
  - Levittown, 1979 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Levittown UFSD, 1987-1990 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Levittown, 1968-1970 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Levittown, 1963 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Levittown 22, 1968-1969 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Lewistown - Porter, 1973-1995 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Lewistown- Porter, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Lewistown- Porter School District, 1991-1995 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Communications Workers, 1978-1990 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Lewistown - Porter, 1970-1978 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Sch. Dist. - Liberty C.S., 2000 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Liberty CSD, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Liberty, 1972-2004 (Box 129, Folder 13)
- Boards of Education: Lima through Lisbon (Box 130)
  - Liberty, 1985-1993 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Lima, 1969-1980 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Limestone, 1988-1995 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Limestone - Sch. Dist., 1991 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Limestone, 1972-1980 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Lindenhurst, 1972 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Lindenhurst, 1970-1997 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Sch. Dist. Lindenhurst P.S., 1990-1997 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Lindenhurst, 1972 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Lindenhurst, 1979-1999 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Lisbon, 1969-2000 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Sch. Dist. - Lisbon C.S., 1996-1998 (Box 130, Folder 12)
- Boards of Education: Lisbon through Liverpool (Box 131)
  - Lisbon, 1970-1978 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Lisbon, 1970-1971 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Little Falls, 1968-1995 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Little Falls, 1979-1997 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Little Falls, 1973 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Little Falls Sch. Dist., 1993-1996 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Little Flower, 1977-1985 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Little Flower S.D., 1993-1995 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Little Valley, 1968-1970 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Little Valley, 1975-1979 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Liverpool - Sch. Dist., 1994 (Box 131, Folder 11)
- Boards of Education: Liverpool through Livonia (Box 132)
  - Liverpool, 1971 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Liverpool, 1992-1994 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Liverpool, 1971-1980 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Liverpool, 1974-1975 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Liverpool, 1985-2003 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Liverpool, 1985-1997 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Livingston Manor, 1975-1977 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Livingston Manor, 1973-2005 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Livingston Manor, 1978-1992 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Livingston Manor (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Livonia, 1973 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Sch. Dist. - Livonia C.S.D., 1996-1998 (Box 132, Folder 12)
- Boards of Education: Livonia through Locust Valley (Box 133)
  - Livonia, 1971-1997 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Livonia, 1990-1994 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Livonia, 1964 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Lockport, 1972-1983 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Lockport CSD, 1996 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Lockport, 1971-1996 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Lockport, 1999-2003 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Lockport, 1972-1973 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Locust Valley, 1968-1979 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Locust Valley, 1971-1988 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Locust Valley, 1970-1983 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Locust Valley - Sch. Dist., 1989-1995 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Locust Valley, 1988-2002 (Box 133, Folder 13)
- Boards of Education: Long Beach through Lowville (Box 134)
  - Long Beach, 1968-1991 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Long Beach Sch. Dist., 1999-2001 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Long Beach, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Long Beach, 1970-1980 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Long Beach, 1973-1989 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Long Lake, 1969-1992 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Longwood, 1986-2002 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Middle Island - Sch. Dist. Longwood SD, 1992-2001 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Lowville, 1969-1975 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Lowville, 1987-1991 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Lowville, 1974-1981 (Box 134, Folder 11)
- Boards of Education: Lowville through Lynbrook (Box 135)
  - Lowville, 1994-2001 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Lowville, 1976-2001 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Lowville, 1974-1980 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Lyncourt, 1999-2001 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Lyme, 1994-1998 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Lyme CS (Chaumont), 2002 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Lyme, 1982-1983 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Lyme, 1982 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Lyme, 1968-1995 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Lynbrook, 1972-1991 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - School Districts - Lynbrook Bd of Educ., 1996-2002 (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Lynbrook, 1973-1977 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Lynbrook, 1971-1981 (Box 135, Folder 13)
- Boards of Education: Lynbrook through Miadson (Box 136)
  - Lynbrook, 1969-1970 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Lyncourt, 1968-2000 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Lyncourt - Sch. Dist., 2002 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Lyncourt, 1972 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Lyndonville - Sch. Dist., 1997-2000 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Lyndonville, 1989 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Lyndonville, 1972 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Lyons, 1968-1998 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Lyons, 1997-2000 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Madison, 1989-1992 (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Madison, 1978-1998 (Box 136, Folder 11)
- Boards of Education: Madison through Maine-Endwell (Box 137)
  - Madison, 1972-1973 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Madrid Waddington, 1968-1992 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Sch. Dist. Madrid - Washington - Washington C.S., 1997-2004 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Madrid Waddington, 1968-1999 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Madrid Waddington - Teachers, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Madrid - Washington (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Mahopac, 1970-1974 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Mahopac, 1975-1990 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Mahopac, 1975-2001 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Mahopac Sch, Dist. Putnam County, 1992-1994 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Mahopac, 1979-1981 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Maine - Endwell, 1969-1991 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Maine-Endwell Central School Dist. + Custodial + Maintenance Assoc., 1980-1989 (Box 137, Folder 13)
- Boards of Education: Maine-Endwell through Malone (Box 138)
  - Maine - Endwell, 1974 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Maine - Endwell, 1970-1997 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Sch. Dist. - Maine - Endwell C.S.D., 1997-2003 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Maine - Endwell, 1982-1997 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Maine - Endwell, 1993-2001 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Malone, 1969-1994 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Malone, 1969-1979 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Malone, 1982-1997 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Malone - Sch. Dist., 1969-1974 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Malone, 1964-1974 (Box 138, Folder 10)
- Boards of Education: Malverne through Mamaroneck (Box 139)
  - Malverne, 1968-1976 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Malverne - Sch. Dist., 1983-2001 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Malverne, 1971-1987 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Malverne, 1979-1999 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Mamoroneck, 1971-1983 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Mamaroneck - Sch. Dist., 1994-1997 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Mamaroneck, 1972 (Box 139, Folder 7)
- Boards of Education: Mamaroneck through Marcus Whitman (Box 140)
  - Mamaroneck Union Free, 1989-2001 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Manhasset, 1974 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Manhasset, 1990-2001 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Manhasset, 1964-1969 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Sch. Dist. - Manhasset, 1994-1996 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Maplewood, 1993-1996 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Manorville, 1972-1973 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Maplewood - Colonies - Teachers, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Marathon, 1968-1969 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Marathon - Sch. Dist., 2002 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Sch. Dist. - Marcellus, 1998 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Marcellus, 1980-1984 (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - Marcellus, 1979-1980 (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - Marcellus, 1969-1972 (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - Marcus Whitman, 1972 (Box 140, Folder 15)
  - Marcus Whitman - Sch. Dist., 1999-2002 (Box 140, Folder 16)
- Boards of Education: Marcus Whitman through Marlboro (Box 141)
  - Marcus Whitman, 1994 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Marcus, 1970-1972 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Margaretville, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Margaretville, 1980 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Marion, 1967-1979 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Marion - Sch. Dist., 1999-2003 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Marion, 1970 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Marion, 1971-1994 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Marion, 1980-1994 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Marlboro - Sch. Dist., 1994-1996 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Marlboro, 1977 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Marlboro, 1968-1972 (Box 141, Folder 12)
- Boards of Education: Marlboro through Massapequa (Box 142)
  - Marlboro, 1987-1991 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Marlboro, 1968-1975 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Maryvale, 1973-1989 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Maryvale, 1970-1973 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Maryvale - Sch. Dist., 1995-2003 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Maryvale School District, 1995-1998 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Maryvale, 1968-1973 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Massapequa, 1968-1974 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Sch. Dist. - Massapequa, 1992-1995 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Massapequa, 1986-1995 (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Massapequa, 1974-1976 (Box 142, Folder 11)
- Boards of Education: Massena through Mayville (Box 143)
  - Massena, 1968-1994 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Sch. Dist. - Massena, 1999-2002 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Massena CSD, 1977-2003 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Massena, 1994-2000 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Massena, 1968-1970 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Mastic Beach, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Mastic Beach, 1969-1972 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Mattituck, 1968-1985 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Mattituck, 1973-1992 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Sch. Dist. - Mattituck N.S., 1996 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Mattituck - Cutchogue (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Mayfield, 1974-2007 (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Sch. Dist. - Mayfield, 1994-1997 (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - Mayfield, 1979 (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Mayville, 1971-1973 (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Mayfield, 1969-1975 (Box 143, Folder 16)
- Boards of Education: Mayville through Medina (Box 144)
  - Mayville, 1972-1981 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Sch. Dist. - Mayville, 1990-1994 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Mayville, 1982-1990 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - McGraw, 1970-1978 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - McGraw - Sch. Dist., 2001-2002 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - McGraw, 1968-1990 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - McGraw, 1970 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Mechanicville, 1972-1999 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Mechanicville (city), 1970-1974 (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Sch. Dist. - Mechanicville City S.D., 1996-1999 (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Mechanicville, 1975-1991 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - Medina, 1969-1975 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - Medina, 1972-1994 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - Medina, 1980-1991 (Box 144, Folder 14)
  - Sch. Dist. - Medina, 1999 (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - Medina, 1970-1973 (Box 144, Folder 16)
- Boards of Education: Menands through Mexico Academy (Box 145)
  - Menands, 1970-1976 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Menands, 1981-2005 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Mepham, 1971-1972 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Merrick, 1968-1986 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Merrick, 1973-1977 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Merrick, 1978-1993 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Merrick, 1986-1995 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Mexico Academy, 1968-1994 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Mexico, 1969-1982 (Box 145, Folder 9)
- Boards of Education: Mexico Academy through Middle Country (Box 146)
  - Middle Country, 1972-1991 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Middle Country, 1971-1980 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Middle Country - Sch. Dist., 1994-2001 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Union F, 1974-1990 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Middle Country, 1969-1986 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Mexico Academy, 1984-1999 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Mexico Academy, 1983-1993 (Box 146, Folder 7)
- Boards of Education: Middle Country through Middletown (Box 147)
  - Middle Country, 1988-1994 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Middle Island, 1976-1992 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Middle Island, 1968-1975 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Middle Island, 1986-1989 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - MiddleBurgh, 1970-1993 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Sch. Dist. - Middleburgh C.S.D., 2000-2003 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Middleburgh, 1971-1996 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Middleburgh, 1975-1996 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - Middletown, 1989-1995 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - Middletown, 1969-1983 (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - Middletown, 1984 (Box 147, Folder 11)
- Boards of Education: Middletown through Miller Place (Box 148)
  - Sch. Dist. Middletown City, 1989-2003 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Middletown, 1972-1988 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Enlarged City School District, 1989-2000 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Milford, 1968-1978 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Milford, 1973 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Milford, 1980-1981 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Sch. Dist. - Milford C.S., 1993-1996 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Milford, 1989 (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Milford, 1973-1987 (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Millbrook, 1980-1989 (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Millbrook, 1973 (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Millbrook - Sch. Dist., 1990-1998 (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - Millbrook, 1973-2004 (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - Miller Place, 1980-1989 (Box 148, Folder 14)
  - Miller Place, 1972-1981 (Box 148, Folder 15)
- Boards of Education: Miller Place through Minisink (Box 149)
  - Sch. Dist. - Miller Place, 1998-2004 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Miller Place, 1970-1973 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Mills, 1971 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Mineola, 1974-1979 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Mineola, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Mineola, 1977-1985 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Mineola, 1985-1991 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Minervia, 1969-1999 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Minerva, 1970-1991 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Minerva, 1980-1989 (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - Minisink, 1968 (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - Minisink, 1969 (Box 149, Folder 12)
- Boards of Education: Minisink Valley through Monroe-Woodbury (Box 150)
  - Sch. Dist. Minisink Valley, 1995-2003 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Minisink, 1971-1973 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Mohawk, 1969-1979 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Mohawk School District, 1996-1998 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Mohawk, 1971 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Mohawk, 1982-1988 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Mohawk, 1994-1995 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Mohansen, 1968-1990 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Mohonasen, 1970-1978 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Mohonsen, 1969-1978 (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - Moira, 1970 (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - Monroe - Woodbury, 1970-1999 (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Monroe - Woodbury, 1972-1981 (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - Sch. Dist. - Monroe - Woodbury, 1985-2001 (Box 150, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: Monroe-Woodbury through Moravia (Box 151)
  - Monroe - Woodbury, 1969-2004 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Montauk, 1970 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Montawk School District, 1993 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Montawk, 1972-1973 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Montauk, 1988 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Sch. Dist. Mont Ice LLd C.S., 1991-1994 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Monticello, 1968-2002 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Monticello, 1972-1986 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Monticello, 1993 (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Monticello, 1989-1990 (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Montrose, 1968-1971 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - Montrose, 1973-1995 (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - Mooers, 1968-1970 (Box 151, Folder 13)
  - Moravia, 1976-1985 (Box 151, Folder 14)
  - Moravia - Sch. Dist., 1996 (Box 151, Folder 15)
- Boards of Education: Moravia through Morristown (Box 152)
  - Moravia, 1975-1989 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Moravia, 1973 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Moravia, 1969-1971 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Moriah school district #1, 1999-2004 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Moriah, 1971-1974 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Moriah, 1970-1983 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Moriah, 1969-1986 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Moriah Central, 1968-1978 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - Morris, 1968-1988 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Morris, 1976-2001 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Morris, 1970-1971 (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - Morris, 1974-2004 (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - Sch. Dist. Morris C.S., 1990-1996 (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Morristown, 1971-1978 (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - Morristown, 1972-1978 (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - Morristown, 1972-1989 (Box 152, Folder 16)
  - Morristown - Sch. Dist., 2000-2005 (Box 152, Folder 17)
- Boards of Education: Morrisville through Mount Pleasant (Box 153)
  - Morrisville - Eaton, 1972-1983 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Morrisville - Eaton, 1977 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Morrisville - Eaton - Sch. Dist., 1994-2000 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Morrisville - Eaton, 1972-1983 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Morrisville - Eaton, 1971 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Mount Murkham, 1968-1981 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Mount Markham, 1985 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Mount Markham C.S., 1994-1998 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Mount Markham, 1983-1993 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Mount Markham, 1983-1993 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Mount Markham, 1990-1992 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Mount Markham, 1990-1993 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Mt. Morris, 1975 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Mt. Morris - Sch. Dist., 1995-2001 (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - Mount Morris, 1968-1986 (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - Mount Morris, 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - Mount Pleasant, 1967-2002 (Box 153, Folder 17)
- Boards of Education: Mount Pleasant through Nanuet (Box 154)
  - Mount Pleasant, 1969-1980 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Mount Pleasant, 1969-1974 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Sch. Dist. - Mount Pleasant C.S.D., 1992-2003 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Mount Pleasant, 1985-1997 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Mt. Sinai, 1976-1987 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Mount Sinai, 1974 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Mt. Sinai UFSD #7, 1997 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Mt. Sinai, 1982 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Mt. Sinai, 1994 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Mt. Upton, 1970-1971 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Mt. Upton Central School, 1972-1982 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - Sch. Dist. - Mount Upton, 1987-1990 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Sch. Dist. Mount Vernon P.S., 1989-1994 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - Mount Vernon, 1973-1984 (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - Mount Vernon, 1969-1982 (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - Mount Vernon, 1973-1976 (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - Mount Vernon City School District, 1999-2004 (Box 154, Folder 17)
  - Mount Vernon, 1968-1971 (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - Manuet, 1968-1971 (Box 154, Folder 19)
- Boards of Education: Nanuet through Nassau (Box 155)
  - Sch. Dist. - Manuet P.S., 1991-1995 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Manuet, 1979-1980 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Manuet, 1971-1973 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Manuet, 1993-2002 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Naples, 1969-1993 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Naples, 1969-1995 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Narrowburg, 1971-1977 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Narrowburg, 1976-1982 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Nassau, 1968-1970 (Box 155, Folder 9)
- Boards of Education: Newcomb through New Hartford (Box 156)
  - Nassau, 1974-1982 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Newcomb Central School District, 2002 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Newcomb Central School District, 1996-2006 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - New Berlin, 1964-1974 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - New Berlin, 1976-1991 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - New Berlin, 1969-1970 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - New Berlin, 1971 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - New Berlin - Sch. Dist., 1989-1994 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - New Berlin, 1987 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - New Castle & Mount Pleasant, 1970 (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - Newfane, 1971-1982 (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - New Hartford, 1978-1994 (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - New Hartford, 1972 (Box 156, Folder 13)
  - New Hartford, 1980-1992 (Box 156, Folder 14)
  - New Hartford, 1968-1997 (Box 156, Folder 15)
- Boards of Education: New Hartford through Newark (Box 157)
  - New Hartford - Sch. Dist., 1994-2000 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - New Hyde Park, 1979 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - New Hyde Park, 1979 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - New Hyde Park, 1971-1974 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - New Hyde Park (Garden Park) - Sch. Dist., 1984-1995 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - New Hyde Park - Garden City Park, 1971-1983 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Sch. Dist. - New Lebanon, 1991-1997 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - New Lebanon, 1972-1991 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - New Lebanon, 1975-1992 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - New Lebanon, 1968-1972 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - New Paltz, 1970-1993 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - New Paltz, 1971-1983 (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Newark, 1979-1985 (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - Newark, 1974 (Box 157, Folder 14)
- Boards of Education: Newark through New Rochelle (Box 158)
  - New Rochelle, 1964-1975 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - New Rochelle, 1981-1983 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - New Rochelle, 1968-1970 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - New Rochelle - Sch. Dist., 1989 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - New Paltz, 1971-1980 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - New Paltz, 1971-1999 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Newark, 1985-1991 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Newark, 1970-1982 (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - Sch. Dist. - Newark, 1992-1996 (Box 158, Folder 9)
- Boards of Education: New Rochelle through New York City (Box 159)
  - New Rochelle, 1966-1986 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - SS-2 Substance Abuse Prev+ Interv. Specialists, 1987-1990 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - WC3 Audio Visual Aides, 1983-1985 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - AD7 Medical Inspectors, 1984 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - CG Grossing Guards, 1982-1990 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - CAF Hourly School Lunch 1243, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - BCI Annual + Monthly Lunch 1241, 1984-1990 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - RN Nurses/ Therapists, 1979-1983 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - AD 6 Directors/ Assistant Dir Substance Abuse, 1984-1987 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - ADI Supervisors/Admin 1237, 1984-1990 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - AID School AIDES 1239, 1984-1990 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Attendance Teachers TA-2 1250, 1982-1987 (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - SS Neighborhood Worker 1246, 1989 (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - PST Admin. Assistants 1245, 1982 (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - SS I Family Worker ST.AL. 1247, 1987-1990 (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - WC2 Buyers Purchase Insp., 1982-1985 (Box 159, Folder 16)
  - WCI Taskforce Monitors 1251, 1984 (Box 159, Folder 17)
  - TA3 Bilingual, 1987-1990 (Box 159, Folder 18)
  - Ad 4 Supv. School Safety, 1987-1990 (Box 159, Folder 19)
  - AD3 Supervisor School Lunch, 1987-1990 (Box 159, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 159, Folder 21)
  - WC5 Film Inspectors Asst., 1989 (Box 159, Folder 22)
  - BC3 Stores Handlers, 1983-1986 (Box 159, Folder 23)
- Boards of Education: New York City through New York City (Box 160)
  - Agreements, UFT, 1972-1990 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - City of New York, 1965-1990 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - City of New York, 1984-1995 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - City of New York, 1975-1991 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - City of New York, 1978-1985 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - City of New York, 1968-1980 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - City of New York, 1979-1983 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - New York, City of, 1982 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - New York City, 1972-1975 (Box 160, Folder 9)
- Boards of Education: New York Mills through Newburgh (Box 161)
  - New York Mills, 1973-1990 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - New York Mills, 1968-1987 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - New York Mills, 1973 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Newark Central, 1989-1992 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Newark Valley, 1968-1987 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Sch. Dist. - Newark Valley, 2001 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Newark Valley, 1973 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Newark Valley, 1973 (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - Newark Valley, 1976-1995 (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - Newburgh, 1971-1984 (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - Newburgh, 1992 (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - Newburgh, 1969-1970 (Box 161, Folder 12)
  - Sch. Dist. - Newburgh, 1994-1997 (Box 161, Folder 13)
- Boards of Education: Newcomb through Niagara Falls (Box 162)
  - Newcomb, 1974 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Newcomb, 1990-1993 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Newcomb, 1987-1989 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Newcomb, 1969-1970 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Newcomb, 1979-1984 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Newfane, 1969-1977 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Newfane, 1983-1989 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Newfane - Sch. Dist., 1989-1995 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Newfane, 1985-1990 (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - Newfane Central School District, 1998-2002 (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - Newark Valley, 1991 (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - Newfield, 1968-1993 (Box 162, Folder 12)
  - Sch. Dist. - Newfield, 1997-2006 (Box 162, Folder 13)
  - Newfield, 1967-1992 (Box 162, Folder 14)
  - Niagara Falls, 1968-1973 (Box 162, Folder 15)
  - Niagara Falls, 1969-1973 (Box 162, Folder 16)
  - Niagara Falls (Box 162, Folder 17)
- Boards of Education: Niagara Falls through Niskayuna (Box 163)
  - Niagara Falls, 1970-1974 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Niagara Falls, 1987-1997 (Box 163, Folder 2)